{
    "subject": "resource/Rhamnus_cathartica",
    "predicate": "ontology/division",
    "object": "resource/Flowering_plant",
    "human_readable": "Rhamnus cathartica belongs to the division of flowering plants.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9635873436927795,
            "question": "Is Rhamnus cathartica a type of flowering plant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9539270997047424,
            "question": "What division do Rhamnus cathartica belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9143204092979431,
            "question": "Give an example of a plant in the same division as Rhamnus cathartica."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6987510323524475,
            "question": "Can you name another plant in the same family as Rhamnus cathartica?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6785664558410645,
            "question": "What are some uses of Rhamnus cathartica?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6705429553985596,
            "question": "Where does Rhamnus cathartica typically grow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4369502663612366,
            "question": "Are there any specific environmental conditions required for Rhamnus cathartica to thrive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2399497628211975,
            "question": "Are there any other types of plants besides flowering plants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21042124927043915,
            "question": "What characteristics define flowering plants?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.016761597245931625,
            "question": "What is the scientific name for common buckthorn?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rhamnus cathartica belongs to the division of flowering plants.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5804_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What characteristics define flowering plants?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5804_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other types of plants besides flowering plants?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5804_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any specific environmental conditions required for Rhamnus cathartica to thrive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5804_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5804_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5804_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5804_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5804_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5804_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5804_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5804_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5804_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5804_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5804_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation result:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The first document mentions that \"Rhamnaceae, is a large family of flowering plants\", which indicates that Rhamnus cathartica belongs to the division of flowering plants."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Rhamnus cathartica is part of the plant kingdom and provide details about its characteristics, including belonging to the family Rhamnaceae. Given that flowering plants (angiosperms) are a subset of seed plants, and all members of the family Rhamnaceae are angiosperms, it can be inferred that Rhamnus cathartica belongs to the division of flowering plants."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}